Love in Taipei is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Arvin Chen.
A young American woman is sent by her parents to a cultural immersion program in
Taipei where she begins a new journey of self-discovery and romance.
Ever Wong, played by Ashley Liao.
Rick Woo, played by Ross Butler.
Xavier Yeh, played by Nico Hiraga.
Sophie Ha, played by Chelsea Zhang.
Auntie Shu, played by Cindy Cheung.
Megan, played by Chloe Fox.
Love in Taipei is a 2023 American romantic comedy film directed by Arvin
Chen, starring Ross Butler, Ashley Liao and Nico Hiraga.
The film is based on Abigail Hing Wen's 2020 novel Loveboat, Taipei.
The film was released by Paramount+ on August 10, 2023.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.